A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.31 (A2005) FA491
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.31 (A2005)
1986-2005
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA491
89.09 Cubic Feet 68 standard record storage boxes.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Separated Materials
Special Formats (digital media, video, audio) have been separated from the body of the collection. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Arrangement
Records are primarily arranged by Program, with some materials arranged by the RF traditional series numbers.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Scope and Contents
Contains grant administration records.
- AC.2005.001: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1995-2004; AC.2005.001; 9.17 Cubic Feet 7 standard record storage boxes, R3701-R3707.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.001.1; 9.17 Cubic Feet 7 record storage boxes
    - RF 99012 #231 - HEARD MUSEUM - PUBLICATION OF EXHIBITION CATALOGUE FOR "REMEMBERING OUR SCHOOL DAYS, 1999-2004 (Box R3701)
    - RF 99012 #232 - ARTS MIDWEST - EXHIBITION, "ILLUSIONS OF EDEN: VISIONS OF THE AMERICAN HEARTLAND", 1998-2004 (Box R3701)
    - RF 99012 #233 - AMIGOS DEL MUSEO DEL BARRIO - "PRESSING THE POINT: PARALLEL EXPRESSIONS IN THE GRAPHIC ARTS OF THE PUERTO RICAN AND CHICANO MOVEMENTS", 1999-2001 (Box R3701)
    - RF 99012 #234 - ASIAN AMERICAN ARTS CENTRE - EXHIBITION, "MILIEU PART III", 1999-2004 (Box R3701)
    - RF 99012 #235 - SAINT LOUIS ART MUSEUM - EXHIBITION, "MASKS: FACES OF CULTURE" AND RELATED PUBLICATION, 1998-2004 (Box R3701)
    - RF 99012 #236 - UNIVERSITY OF IOWA - EXHIBITION, "RENEWING TRADITION: REVITALIZATION OF BOGOLAN IN MALI AND ABROAD", 1998-2001 (Box R3701)
    - RF 99012 #237 - MERCED COUNTY HISTORICAL SOCIETY - EXHIBITION, "FORTY ACRE DREAMS", 1999-2000 (Box R3701)
    - RF 99012 #239 - ATLANTA HISTORICAL SOCIETY - EXHIBITION, "NATIVE LANDS: INDIANS AND GEORGIA", 1999-2000 (Box R3701)
    - RF 99012 #240 - WILLIAMS COLLEGE - "CARRIE MAE WEEMS: THE HAMPTON PROJECT", 1998-2001 (Box R3701)
    - RF 99012 #241 - MEXICAN MUSEUM - EXHIBITION, "COVARRUBIAS: THE MIGUEL AND ROSA COVARRUBIAS COLLECTION", 1999-2002 (Box R3701)
    - RF 99012 #243 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - MEETING TO PLAN CONFERENCE, "MUSEUMS IN THE GLOBAL SPHERE", 2000 (Box R3701)
    - RF 99016 #19 - STRATEGIC ACTIONS FOR A JUST ECONOMY - DIRECT DEPOSIT BANKING FOR WELFARE RECIPIENTS IN LOS ANGELES, 1999-2000 (Box R3702)
    - RF 99014 #18 - INTERDENOMINATIONAL THEOLOGICAL CENTER - ASSIST BLACK THEOLOGIANS IN ADDRESSING COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT CHALLENGES OF THE 21ST CENTURY, 1999-2004 (Box R3702)
    - RF 99014 #19 - UNIVERSITY OF MINNESOTA - ENGAGE COMMUNITIES OF COLOR IN ISSUES ADDRESSING POVERTY, REGIONALISM, AND METROPOLITAN EQUITY, 1998-2002 (Box R3702)
    - RF 99014 #21 - GRADUATE SCHOOL AND UNIVERSITY CENTER, CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - PROJECT FORUM ON RACE AND DEMOCRACY, 1999-2002 (Box R3702)
    - RF 99014 #25 - CONSERVATION LAW FOUNDATION - SEAPORT PROJECT, 1996-2000 (Box R3702)
    - RF 99015 #40 - INTERNATIONAL LABOUR ORGANISATION (SWITZERLAND) - MEETINGS OF ADVISORY GROUP; ENTERPRISE LABOUR FLEXIBILITY AND SECURITY SURVEYS, 1999-2000 (Box R3702)
    - RF 99015 #50 - ASPEN INSTITUTE - DOMESTIC STRATEGY GROUP, 1998-2000 (Box R3702)
    - RF 99016 #21 - LOS ANGELES ALLIANCE FOR A NEW ECONOMY - SUBSIDY ACCOUNTABILITY PROJECT, 1999-2000 (Box R3702)
    - RF 99016 #22 - FINANCIAL MARKETS CENTER - INCREASE UNDERSTANDING OF FINANCIAL MARKET DYNAMICS, ECONOMIC TRENDS, FEDERAL RESERVE SYSTEM OPERATIONS, 1999-2001 (Box R3702)
    - RF 99016 #24 - NATIONAL INTERFAITH COMMITTEE FOR WORKER JUSTICE - WORKER JUSTICE FUND, 1999-2003 (Box R3702)
    - RF 99016 #26 - UNIVERSITY OF WASHINGTON - IMPLEMENTATION AND IMPACTS OF THE SECOND YEAR OF WASHINGTON STATE'S COMMUNITY JOBS PROGRAM, 1998-2001 (Box R3702)
    - RF 99016 #29 - UNEMPLOYMENT INFORMATION CENTER - WELFARE TO WORK EFFORTS IN PENNSYLVANIA, 1999-2002 (Box R3702)
    - RF 98028 #320; RF 99023 #321 - FILM ARTS FOUNDATION - CONFERENCE, "AS WORLDS COLLIDE", 1998-2001 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99020 #195 - BRITISH ASSOCIATION FOR BETTER LAND HUSBANDRY (ENGLAND) - ORGANIC MATTER NETWORK IN AFRICA, 1991-2001 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99020 #205 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - ECONOMICS AND POLICY WORKING GROUP FOR SMALLHOLDER FOOD SECURITY IN AFRICA, 1999-2002 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99020 #206 - ZIMBABWE - LANDS AND AGRICULTURE (MINISTRY OF) - POLICY DIALOGUE THROUGH AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTION FOOD SECURITY TASK FORCE, 1999-2002 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99020 #216 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY (KENYA) - WORKSHOPS ON LAKE VICTORIA BASIN AND E. AFRICAN HIGHLANDS, 1999-2002 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99020 #220 - MICHIGAN STATE UNIVERSITY - KENYA FERTILIZER MARKET STUDY, 1999-2003 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99020 #223 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - WORKSHOP ON ENVIRONMENTAL MANAGEMENT AND POVERTY ALLEVIATION IN LAKE VICTORIA BASIN, 2000-2001 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99023 #323 - PENNSYLVANIA STATE UNIVERSITY - SYMPOSIUM, "PERFORMATIVE SITES", 1999-2001 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #383 - BEBE MILLER CO. - DANCE THEATER WORK, "MAP OF THE BODY", 1999-2004 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #384 - BOYS AND GIRLS CLUBS OF METRO ATLANTA - PERFORMANCE WORK, "GIRLS AND", 1998-2001 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #385 - BUILDERS ASSOCIATION - MULTl-MEDIA THEATER WORK, "OPERA", 1999-2002 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #386 - CENTER FOR CULTURAL EXCHANGE - RESIDENCY AND COLLABORATION, "AFRICA/AMERICA", 1999-2003 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #387 - CHILDREN'S THEATRE CO. - "THE VERY OLD MAN WITH ENORMOUS WINGS", 1999-2001 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #388 - CROSSROADS THEATRE CO. - THEATER WORK, "YELLOW EYES", 1999-2002 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #389 - IDRIS ACKAMOOR AND CULTURAL ODYSSEY - "CAN WE GET THERE BY CANDLELIGHT", 1999-2001 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #391 - DANCE BRAZIL - DANCE THEATER WORK, "A ESCRAVA ANASTACIA", 1999-2000 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #392 - DANCING IN THE STREETS - SITE-SPECIFIC LIVING INSTALLATION, "NIGHT LIGHT", 1999-2001 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #393 - DOWNTOWN ARTS PROJECTS - MULTI-MEDIA TRILOGY, "THE LANDSCHAFT PROJECT", 1999-2002 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #395 - EIKO AND KOMA - DANCE WORK, "WHEN NIGHTS WERE DARK", 1999-2004 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #396 - ELEVATOR REPAIR SERVICE - THEATER WORK, "WHITE PLASTIC SHELL", 1999-2002 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #397 - FOUNDRY THEATRE - THEATER WORK, "TALK", 1999-2001 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #398 - GOODMAN THEATRE - THEATER WORK, "BOY MEETS GIRL", 1999-2000 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #399 - HERE - "NIGHT VISION", 1999-2000 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99024 #400 - HEART OF THE BEAST THEATRE - "SEED: AWESOME VESSEL OF POWER", 1999-2001 (Box R3703)
    - RF 99028 #42 - CORPORATION FOR SUPPORTIVE HOUSING - DISSEMINATE LESSONS AND BEST PRACTICE FOR NEXT STEP: JOBS, 1999-2002 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99026 #84 - STONE CIRCLES - TRAIN NONPROFIT ORGANIZATIONS IN REFLECTIVE SPIRITUAL PRACTICE, 1999-2002 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99024 #401 - GOODE PERFORMANCE GROUP - DANCE WORK, "UNDERTAKING HARRY", 1999-2000 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99024 #404 - KRONOS QUARTET - MUSICAL PERFORMANCE, "TONIGHT IS THE NIGHT", 1999-2000 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99024 #405 - LINES CONTEMPORARY BALLET - BALLET WITH TANGO MUSIC, 1999-2000 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99024 #406 - LERMAN DANCE EXCHANGE - "HALLELUJAH" SERIES - DANCE WORKS, "IN PRAISE OF", 1999-2004 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99024 #408 - MUSE, CINCINNATI'S WOMEN'S CHOIR - "NEW SPIRITUALS PROJECT", 1999-2001 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99024 #409 - MUSICAL TRADITIONS - CHAMBER MUSIC WORKS, 1999-2004 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99024 #410 - NEW CITY THEATER - "SNOW", 1999-2000 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99024 #411 - ONTOLOGICAL-HYSTERIC THEATRE - "BAD BOY NIETZSCHE", 1999-2001 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99024 #413 - PAINTED BRIDE ART CENTER - SPOKEN HAND RESIDENCY PROJECT, 1999-2001 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99024 #415 - PLAYWRIGHTS HORIZONS - MUSICAL THEATER WORK, "THE BUBBLY BLACK GIRL", 1999-2001 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99026 #85 - CITYKIDS FOUNDATION - YOUTH-ORI ENTED PERFORMANCE PIECES ON ISSUES OF DEMOCRACY, 1999-2002 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99026 #86 - NATIONAL NETWORK FOR IMMIGRANT AND REFUGEE RIGHTS - VIDEO ON GLOBAL ECONOMY AND INTERNATIONAL MIGRATION, 1999-2001 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99026 #87 - WORKING TODAY - PORTABLE BENEFITS FOR NEW MOBILE WORK FORCE, 1999-2001 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99026 #88 - PARENTS INTERNATIONAL ETHIOPIA - TRAINING FOR ETHIOPIAN RURAL WOMEN IN LEADERSHIP AND DEMOCRACY, 1999 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99026 #89 - INTERCULTURAL DEVELOPMENT RESEARCH ASSOCIATION - INTERCHANGE IDEAS OF DEMOCRACY, FREEDOM AND LEADERSHIP AMONG STUDENTS USING VIDEO-CONFERENCING, 1999 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99026 #90 - ROCKY MOUNTAIN YOUTH CORPS - DIALOGUE ON POTENTIAL CROSS-SECTOR COLLABORATIONS TOWARD PROMOTING DEMOCRACY, 1999-2001 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99026 #91 - ROCKY MOUNTAIN YOUTH CORPS - ESTABLISH NATIONAL INSTITUTE WITHIN THE YOUTH CORPS, 1999 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99026 #94 - ROCKY MOUNTAIN YOUTH CORPS - YOUTH LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1999-2000 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99026 #96 - ISLES, INC, - BUILD OPERATIONAL CAPACITY OF INTERNATIONAL AND DOMESTIC COMMUNITY-BASED ORGANIZATIONS, 1999-2002 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99026 #98 - FOR LOVE OF CHILDREN - LEADERSHIP CURRICULUM FOR WOMEN OF COLOR IN WASHINGTON, D.C., 1999 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99026 #99 - FOR LOVE OF CHILDREN - RESIDENT-LED EFFORTS TO STRENGTHEN FAMILIES AND ASSIST IN YOUTH DEVELOPMENT IN THE WASHINGTON, D.C. AREA, 1999 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99027 #1 - PHILANTHROPIC INITIATIVE - DONOR RESOURCES PROJECT, 1999-2002 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99028 #45 - UNITED WAY OF THE BAY AREA - SAN FRANCISCO WORKS EMPLOYMENT SERVICES, 1997-1999 (Box R3704)
    - RF 99029 #18 - JOBS FOR THE FUTURE - LOCAL AND NATIONAL CAPACITY FOR WORKFORCE DEVELOPMENT IN THE U.S. AND U.K., 1999-2001 (Box R3705)
    - RF 99028 #49 - MANPOWER DEMONSTRATION RESEARCH CORPORATION - SAN FRANCISCO WORKS' WELFARE-TO-WORK PROGRAM, 1999-2001 (Box R3705)
    - RF 99029 #15 - INDIANAPOLIS PRIVATE INDUSTRY COUNCIL - CONFERENCE, "CREATING OPPORTUNITIES THROUGH WORK", 1999-2004 (Box R3705)
    - RF 99028 #50 - COMMUNITY PARTNERS - COMMUNITY SUPPORTS FOR WORK FELLOWSHIP, 1999-2001 (Box R3705)
    - RF 99028 #52 - CONSENSUS ORGANIZING INSTITUTE - WELFARE-TO-WORK IN SAN DIEGO, 1999-2000 (Box R3705)
    - RF 99029 #16 - GREATER BALTIMORE ALLIANCE FOUNDATION - SERVICE SECTOR MOBILITY PROJECT, 1999-2002 (Box R3705)
    - RF 99029 #20 - PUBLIC/PRIVATE VENTURES - TRANSITIONAL WORK PROGRAM IN PHILADELPHIA, 1998-2002 (Box R3705)
    - RF 99030 - BUILDING COMMUNITY, 1997-1998 (Box R3705)
    - RF 99030 #35 - EZ/EC FOUNDATION CONSORTIUM - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1995-2004 (Box R3705, Box R3706)
    - RF 99030 #35 - EZ/EC FOUNDATION CONSORTIUM - GENERAL SUPPORT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1995-2004 (Box R3705, Box R3706)
    - RF 99032 #107 - COMMUNITY SCHOOL DISTRICT 13 - IMPLEMENTATION OF COMER SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM, 1994-2001 (Box R3706)
    - RF 99032 #107 - COMMUNITY SCHOOL DISTRICT 13 - IMPLEMENTATION OF COMER SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-2001 (Box R3706)
    - RF 99036 #5 - SREE CHITRA TIRUNAL INSTITUTE FOR MEDICAL SCIENCES AND TECHNOLOGY (INDIA) - ANNUAL MEETING OF PHSWOW NETWORK, 1999-2004 (Box R3707)
    - RF 99036 #8 - (STRENGTHENING PUBLIC HEALTH PRACTICE IN ZIMBABWE AND ELSEWHERE) - PHSWOW EVALUATION, 2000-2001 (Box R3707)
    - RF 99038 #6 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION (SWITZERLAND) - TUBERCULOSIS DIAGNOSTIC INITIATIVE, 1999-2001 (Box R3707)
    - RF 99038 #8 - EMPRESA COLOMBIANA DE PRODUCTOS VERTERINARIOS S. A. (VECOL) - SEMINAR ON "FUTURE PROSPECTS FOR VACCINE PRODUCTION TECHNOLOGY", 1999-2000 (Box R3707)
    - RF 99039 #3 - INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT RESEARCH CENTRE (CANADA) - PUBLICATION OF PROCEEDINGS FROM WORKSHOP ON ECOSYSTEM APPROACH TO HUMAN HEALTH, 1999-2002 (Box R3707)
    - RF 99039 #4 - (DISEASE SURVEILLANCE) - STRENGTHENING DISEASE SURVEILLANCE IN EAST AFRICA, 1999-2001 (Box R3707)
    - RF 99043 #21 - ISLAMIC-CHRISTIAN NATIONAL DIALOGUE COMMITTEE (LEBANON) - INTER-RELIGIOUS ACTIVITIES AND PEACE PROCESS IN MIDDLE EAST, 1999-2004 (Box R3707)
- AC.2005.009: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1991-2004; AC.2005.009; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 standard record storage boxes, R3708-R3712.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2005.009.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - RF 99050 - MEXICAN AMERICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND, INC. - PUBLIC UNDERSTANDING OF AFFIRMATIVE ACTION, 1996-2001 (Box R3708)
    - RF 99050 - MEXICAN AMERICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND, INC. - PUBLIC UNDERSTANDING OF AFFIRMATIVE ACTION - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1996-2001 (Box R3708)
    - RF 99055 #170 - UNITED NATIONS CHILDREN'S FUND - ALLIANCE FOR COMMUNITY ACTION ON FEMALE EDUCATION, 1996-2004 (Box R3708)
    - RF 99055 #171 - UNITED NATIONS CHILDREN'S FUND - MEETINGS ON FEMALE EDUCATION, 1999-2002 (Box R3708)
    - RF 99055 #177 - (FEMALE PARTICIPATION IN AFRICAN EDUCATION) - CONSULTATIVE MEETING ON LEARNING COMPETENCIES AND SEXUAL MATURATION, 2000-2002 (Box R3708)
  - Creativity and Culture (CC), AC.2005.009.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 CC 002 - BRANDYWINE WORKSHOP - "HIDDEN IMAGES: CUBAN CONTEMPORARY GRAPHIC ART", 1999-2001 (Box R3709)
    - 2000 CC 010 - NATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF ARTISTS' ORGANIZATIONS - TWELFTH NATIONAL CONFERENCE, 2000-2002 (Box R3709)
    - 2000 CC 014 - COMPUTER PROFESSIONALS FOR SOCIAL RESPONSIBILITY - SYMPOSIUM, "SHAPING THE NETWORK SOCIETY", 2000-2004 (Box R3709)
    - 2000 CC 027 - NEW HAVEN INTERNATIONAL FESTIVAL OF ARTS AND IDEAS - 2000 FESTIVAL, 2000-2001 (Box R3709)
    - 2000 CC 033 - CREATIVE TIME - "CREATIVE TIME IN THE ANCHORAGE 2000" (Box R3709)
    - 2000 CC 035 - CITY PARKS FOUNDATION - SUMMERSTAGE 2000, 2000-2001 (Box R3709)
    - 2000 CC 040 - PERFORMING ARTS LABS (ENGLAND} - LIT LAB II, 2000-2004 (Box R3709)
  - Communication for Social Change (CS), AC.2005.009.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 CS 001 - INTERNATIONAL COUNCIL OF AIDS SERVICE ORGANIZATIONS (CANADA) - ASSIST DEVELOPING COUNTRIES TO PARTICIPATE IN WORLD-WIDE AIDS DEBATE, 2000-2001 (Box R3709)
  - Food Security (FS), AC.2005.009.4; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2000 FS 007 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF RURAL RECONSTRUCTION - WORKSHOP ON SUSTAINABLE AGRICULTURE, 2000-2001 (Box R3709)
    - 2000 FS 009 - UNIVERSITY OF BERNE (SWITZERLAND} - LAIKIPIA RESEARCH PROGRAMME, 1991-2003 (Box R3709)
    - 2000 FS 030 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - WORKSHOP ON SUSTAINABLE SEED SYSTEMS FOR SMALL-SCALE FARMERS IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2000-2002 (Box R3709)
    - 2000 FS 061 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - FIFTH TRIENNIAL CONGRESS OF EAST AFRICA POTATO ASSOCIATION (Box R3709)
    - 2000 FS 086 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - FOURTH INTERNATIONAL RICE GENETICS SYMPOSIUM, 2000-2001 (Box R3710)
  - Global Inclusion (GI), AC.2005.009.5; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - 2000 GI 001 - EARTH TIMES FOUNDATION - SOUTH-SOUTH PARTNERSHIP INITIATIVE, 1996-2001 (Box R3710)
    - 2000 GI 002 - EQUILIBRES ET POPULATIONS (FRANCE) - NEWSLETTER ON POPULATION AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH, 1994-2001 (Box R3710)
    - 2000 GI 003 - AFRICAN BIOTECHNOLOGY STAKEHOLDERS FORUM (KENYA) - WORKSHOP ON BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1999-2004 (Box R3710)
    - 2000 GI 011 - BELLAGIO FORUM FOR SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT (GERMANY) - ITS ACTIVITIES IN SUSTAINABLE ECOLOGICAL DEVELOPMENT, 1993-2002 (Box R3711)
    - 2000 GI 011 - BELLAGIO FORUM FOR SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT (GERMANY) - ITS ACTIVITIES IN SUSTAINABLE ECOLOGICAL DEVELOPMENT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1993-2002 (Box R3711)
    - 2000 GI 013 - SWEDISH ASSOCIATION FOR SEX EDUCATION (SWEDEN) - PUBLIC EDUCATION PROJECT, 1997-2001 (Box R3711)
    - 2000 GI 031 - RURAL ADVANCEMENT FOUNDATION INTERNATIONAL (CANADA) - CSO REPRESENTATIVE PARTICIPATION IN CONFERENCES, 2000-2001 (Box R3711)
    - 2000 GI 032 - CHIANG MAI UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUN ON MMSEA, 2000-2003 (Box R3711)
    - 2000 GI 039 - GLOBE USA - GLOBALIZATION AND ROLE OF LEGISLATORS, 2000-2003 (Box R3711)
    - 2000 GI 052 - (GLOBAL INCLUSION) - CROSS-THEMATIC PROGRAM ON WATER, 2000-2001 (Box R3712)
    - 2000 GI 053 - DILLE, JOHN E. - "PLANT BIOTECHNOLOGY QUARTERLY", 2000-2004 (Box R3712)
    - 2000 GI 060 - GLOBAL BIODIVERSITY INSTITUTE - TRAINING IN BIODIVERSITY, BIOTECHNOLOGY AND LAW, 2000-2002 (Box R3712)
    - 2000 GI 067 - SOUTH CENTRE (SWITZERLAND) - WORKSHOP ON BIOSAFETY PROTOCOL, 2000-2002 (Box R3712)
    - 2000 GI 100 - BLACK, STEPHANIE KAREN - DOCUMENTARY FILM "NO COUNTRY IS AN ISLAND" (Box R3712)
  - Health Equity (HE), AC.2005.009.6; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 HE 007 - PANOS LIMITED (ENGLAND) - AIDS BRIEFING DOCUMENT, 2000-2002 (Box R3712)
    - 2000 HE 019 - COUNCIL ON HEALTH RESEARCH FOR DEVELOPMENT (SWITZERLAND) - CONFERENCE ON HEALTH RESEARCH, 1999-2001 (Box R3712)
    - 2000 HE 021 - (HEALTH EQUITY) - TB ALLIANCE, 2000-2001 (Box R3712)
    - 2000 HE 047 - (HEALTH EQUITY) - "SCIENTIFIC BLUE PRINT FOR TB DRUG DEVELOPMENT", PUBLICATION, 2000-2001 (Box R3712)
  - Population and Cairo Agenda (PC), AC.2005.009.7; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 PC 001 - (POPULATION AND CAIRO AGENDA) - EXPLORATIONS, 1999-2000 (Box R3712)
- AC.2005.011: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2005; AC.2005.011; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3713-R3716.
  - Population and Cairo Agenda (PC), AC.2005.011.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - 2000 PC 010 - POPULATION COUNCIL - RENOVATION OF CENTER FOR BIOMEDICAL RESEARCH, 1999-2001 (Box R3712)
    - 2000 PC 013 - (POPULATION AND CAIRO AGENDA) - FUTURE GRANTMAKING IN POPULATION AND PUBLIC HEALTH IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 2000-2002 (Box R3713)
    - 2000 PC 014 - BANARAS HINDU UNIVERSITY - WOMEN AND FERTILITY IN EASTERN UTTAR PRADESH, 1993-2000 (Box R3713)
  - Program Venture Experiment (PV), AC.2005.011.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 PV 001 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - CHANDLER SYMPOSIUM ON RICE RESEARCH, 1999-2000 (Box R3713)
    - 2000 PV 004 - (SPECIAL PROGRAMS) - GLOBAL SECURITY ISSUES, 2000-2002 (Box R3713)
  - Regional Nairobi (RN), AC.2005.011.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - 2000 RN 003 - INTERNATIONAL ASSOCIATION OF STUDENTS INTERESTED IN ECONOMICS AND BUSINESS MANAGEMENT - KENYA - SEMINAR AND FORUM TO PROMOTE AFRICA RENAISSANCE, 2000-2003 (Box R3713)
    - 2000 RN 011 - ASSOCIATION FOR BETTER LAND HUSBANDRY (KENYA) - A POVERTY ASSESSMENT STUDY, 2000-2003 (Box R3713)
  - Working Communities (WC), AC.2005.011.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage boxes
    - 2000 WC 009 - COMMUNITY PARTNERS - LUCY ESQUIBEL MEMORIAL FUND, 2000-2002 (Box R3713)
    - 2000 WC 015 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (SANTA BARBARA) - INSTITUTIONS OF HIGHER EDUCATION AND COMMUNITY PARTNERSHIP CONFERENCE, 1998-2002 (Box R3713)
    - 2000 WC 018 - COLLINS CENTER FOR PUBLIC POLICY - CONFERENCE, "SMART INVESTING IN CALIFORNIA COMMUNITIES", 2000-2003 (Box R3713)
    - 2000 WC 019 - MANPOWER DEMONSTRATION RESEARCH CORPORATION - WISCONSIN WORKS IN MILWAUKEE COUNTY, 1997-2001 (Box R3713)
    - 2000 WC 050 - MANPOWER DEMONSTRATION RESEARCH CORPORATION - WORKSHOP TO ASSESS AND ANALYZE PUBLICATION RE JOBS PLUS, 2000-2001 (Box R3713)
    - 2000 WC 092 - STATE UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK (ALBANY) - STATE CAPACITY STUDY, 2000-2002 (Box R3713)
    - 2000 WC 098 - CENTER FOR LAW AND SOCIAL POLICY - CONFERENCE, "FAMILY FORMATION, POVERTY AND WELFARE REFORM", 2000-2002 (Box R3713)
  - Arts and Humanities (AH), AC.2005.011.5; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - AH 9607 - WOMEN'S WORLD ORGANIZATION FOR RIGHTS, LITERATURE AND DEVELOPMENT - BC CONFERENCE: GENDER-BASED CENSORSHIP, 1995-1999 (Box R3714)
    - AH 9707 - BC CONFERENCE: ETHNIC CONFLICT AND ETHNIC DIVIDE, 1997-2000 (Box R3714)
    - AH 9905 - THEATRE COMMUNICATIONS GROUP - WEBSITE FOR NOT-FOR-PROFIT PROFESSIONAL THEATER COMMUNITY, 1999-2001 (Box R3714)
    - AH 9938 - WOMEN'S WORLD ORGANIZATION FOR RIGHTS, LITERATURE AND DEVELOPMENT - NETWORK OF WOMEN WRITERS IN AFRICA, 1999-2001 (Box R3714)
    - AH 9942 - AMERICAN ASS EMBLY - INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY AND ARTS AND CULTURAL SECTOR, 1999-2001 (Box R3714)
    - AH 9944 - CITY LORE: THE NEW YORK CENTER FOR URBAN FOLK CULTURE - "THE PEOPLE'S POETRY GATHERING", 1997-2004 (Box R3714)
  - African Initiatives (AI), AC.2005.011.6; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - AI 9617 - SOCIAL SCIENCE RESEARCH COUNCIL - BC CONFERENCE: CROSS-NATIONAL CAPACITY BUILDING, 1996-1999 (Box R3714)
    - AI 9707 - TURKANA WOMEN CONFERENCE CENTRE (KENYA) - WOMEN LEADERSHIP COURSE, 1996-2003 (Box R3714)
    - AI 9810 - ROCKEFELLER FOUDATION - GLOBAL INFORMATION/COMMUNICATION SYSTEMS IN AFRICA, 1996-2002 (Box R3714)
    - AI 9811 - PAN-AMERICAN STUDIES AND RESEARCH CENTER IN INT'L RELATIONS AND EDUCATION FOR DEVELOPMENT (COTE D'IVOIRE) - SEMINAR ON "REFORM AND INNOVATIONS IN HIGHER EDUCATION IN AFRICA" AND "JEDIRAF" JOURNAL, 1998-2002 (Box R3714)
    - AI 9813 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH RESEARCH IN SUB-SAHARAN AFRICA, 1998-2002 (Box R3714)
    - AI 9908 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - PUBLICATION, "TRANSFORMATION AND CHALLENGES TO DEVELOPMENT IN UGANDA", 1999-2002 (Box R3714)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS), AC.2005.011.7; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - AS 9442 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - BC TEAM: CHARACTERIZATION OF AFRICAN AGRICULTURAL SYSTEMS, 1994-1998 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9702 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL DEVELOPMENT - POLICY UNITS, 1996-2001 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9710 - WYE COLLEGE (ENGLAND) - EXTERNAL PROGRAMME TRAINING, 1996-2004 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9714 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - EVALUATE AND IMPLEMENT A SOIL MANAGEMENT PACKAGE FOR VARIABLE RAINFALL CONDITIONS, 1994-2002 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9725 - KIHURANI, AGNES - SWEET POTATO STORAGE ROOTS SPOILAGE IN KENYA, 1997-2001 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9813 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - IN-COUNTRY WORKSHOP, 1997-2002 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9814 - CENTER FOR THE APPLICATION OF MOLECULAR BIOLOGY TO INTERNATIONAL AGRICULTURE (AUSTRALIA) - BC CONFERENCE: ASEXUAL SEED REPRODUCTION IN CEREALS, 1997-1998 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9847 - UNIVERSITY OF ZIMBABWE - TECHNICAL AND MANAGEMENT BACKUP FOR SOYABEAN PROMOTION PROGRAM, 1998-2002 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9901 - LWOLE, CHARLES LWANGA - AFRICAN CASSAVA MOSAIC DISEASE IN WESTERN KENYA, 1998-2002 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9914 - UNITED STATES - AGRICULTURE (DEPT. OF) - PLANT AND ANIMAL GENOME VIII MEETING, 1999-2002 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9918 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - EXPLORATION INITIATIVES, 1998-2001 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9919 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY (KENYA) - WORKSHOP AND BOOK ON NATURAL RESOURCE MANAGEMENT AND SUSTAINABLE AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTION, 1998-2002 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9921 - INDIAN INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, DELHI - GLOBAL WARMING AND INDIA'S FOOD SECURITY, 1998-2003 (Box R3715)
    - AS 9926 - WINROCK INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE FOR AGRICULTURAL DEVELOPMENT - GUIDELINES FOR NEW TECHNOLOGIES IN AGROBIOTECHNOLOGY, 1999-2001 (Box R3715)